title,description,published,link,source_url,crawled_at,analysis,financial_metrics
Yahoo Finance Presents: Ford President & CEO Jim Farley,"<p>Ford President and CEO Jim Farley joins Yahoo Finance’s Pras Subramanian at the Red Bull Event in New York City to discuss its partnership with Red Bull, its return to Formula 1, and the growth of the company.</p>","Mon, 13 Feb 2023 19:27:47 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Ford', 'ORG'), ('Jim Farley', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('the Red Bull Event', 'ORG'), ('New York City', 'GPE'), ('Red Bull', 'ORG'), ('Formula 1', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.04545454545454545, 'keywords': ['p', 'Ford', 'President', 'CEO', 'Jim', 'Farley', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Pras', 'Subramanian', 'Red', 'Bull', 'Event', 'New', 'York', 'City', 'discuss', 'partnership', 'Red', 'Bull', 'return', 'Formula', 'growth']}","{'numbers': ['1'], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Harvey Mason Jr., Recording Academy CEO","<p>Yahoo Finance’s Jennifer Schonberger sits down with Recording Academy CEO, Harvey Mason Jr., as they discuss the 2023 Grammy Awards, diversity in the Recording Academy, and challenges facing the music industry.</p>","Mon, 13 Feb 2023 19:25:04 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Jennifer Schonberger', 'PERSON'), ('Recording Academy', 'ORG'), ('Harvey Mason Jr.', 'ORG'), ('the Recording Academy', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.15555555555555559, 'keywords': ['p', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Jennifer', 'Schonberger', 'sits', 'Recording', 'Academy', 'CEO', 'Harvey', 'Mason', 'discuss', 'Grammy', 'Awards', 'diversity', 'Recording', 'Academy', 'challenges', 'facing', 'music']}","{'numbers': ['2023'], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: IMF Chief Economist Pierre-Olivier Gourinchas,"<p>IMF Chief Economist Pierre-Olivier Gourinchas sits down with Yahoo Finance’s Jennifer Schonberger to speak about the state of the global economy in 2023, including the energy market, unemployment, and recession fears.</p>","Mon, 13 Feb 2023 19:20:21 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Pierre-Olivier Gourinchas', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Jennifer Schonberger', 'PERSON'), ('2023', 'DATE')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['p', 'IMF', 'Chief', 'Economist', 'Pierre', 'Olivier', 'Gourinchas', 'sits', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Jennifer', 'Schonberger', 'speak', 'state', 'global', 'economy', 'including', 'energy', 'market', 'unemployment', 'recession']}","{'numbers': ['2023'], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Mario Dedivanovic, Makeup by Mario Founder & CEO","<p>Yahoo Finance’s Brooke DiPalma and Alexandra Canal sit down with Makeup by Mario Founder &amp; CEO, Mario Dedivanovic, as they discuss the brand, selling products in Sephora, social media, and Mario’s career journey.</p>","Wed, 28 Dec 2022 17:02:44 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Brooke DiPalma', 'PERSON'), ('Alexandra Canal', 'PERSON'), ('Makeup', 'PERSON'), ('Mario Founder &', 'ORG'), ('Mario Dedivanovic', 'PERSON'), ('Sephora', 'GPE'), ('Mario', 'PERSON'), ('journey.</p', 'PERSON')], 'sentiment': -0.06111111111111113, 'keywords': ['p', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Brooke', 'DiPalma', 'Alexandra', 'Canal', 'sit', 'Makeup', 'Mario', 'Founder', 'amp', 'CEO', 'Mario', 'Dedivanovic', 'discuss', 'brand', 'selling', 'products', 'Sephora', 'social', 'media', 'Mario', 'career']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Andy Cohen, TV Host, Producer, & Author","<p>Yahoo Finance's Alexandra Canal sits down with TV Host, Producer, &amp; Author, Andy Cohen, as they discuss 'The Real Housewives' franchise, the Bravo brand, and how Andy is preparing for the holiday season.</p>","Thu, 15 Dec 2022 16:23:32 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [(""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('Alexandra Canal', 'PERSON'), ('Producer', 'GPE'), ('Author', 'GPE'), ('Andy Cohen', 'PERSON'), ('Bravo', 'NORP'), ('Andy', 'PERSON')], 'sentiment': 0.022222222222222213, 'keywords': ['p', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Alexandra', 'Canal', 'sits', 'TV', 'Host', 'Producer', 'amp', 'Author', 'Andy', 'Cohen', 'discuss', 'Real', 'Housewives', 'franchise', 'Bravo', 'brand', 'Andy', 'preparing', 'holiday']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Tony award-winning actress and singer Idina Menzel,"<p>Tony award-winning actress and singer Idina Menzel sits down with Yahoo Finance’s Alexandra Canal to speak about her new documentary, her career on the stage and in films, and the return of Bob Iger to Disney.</p>","Thu, 15 Dec 2022 16:16:50 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Tony', 'PERSON'), ('Idina', 'GPE'), ('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Alexandra Canal', 'PERSON'), ('Bob Iger', 'PERSON')], 'sentiment': -0.006397306397306411, 'keywords': ['p', 'Tony', 'award', 'winning', 'actress', 'singer', 'Idina', 'Menzel', 'sits', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Alexandra', 'Canal', 'speak', 'new', 'documentary', 'career', 'stage', 'films', 'return', 'Bob', 'Iger']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Grammy-nominated recording artist and entrepreneur Fat Joe,"<p>Grammy-nominated recording artist and entrepreneur Fat Joe sat down with Yahoo Finance’s Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi to talk about his new book ‘The Book of Jose: a memoir,’ growing up in the South Bronx, and the developments in his career that got him to where he is now.</p>","Thu, 17 Nov 2022 16:59:23 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Fat Joe', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('‘The Book of Jose: a memoir', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the South Bronx', 'LOC')], 'sentiment': -0.009595959595959616, 'keywords': ['p', 'Grammy', 'nominated', 'recording', 'artist', 'entrepreneur', 'Fat', 'Joe', 'sat', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'talk', 'new', 'book', 'Book', 'Jose', 'memoir', 'growing', 'South', 'Bronx', 'developments', 'career', 'got']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Michael Miebach, Mastercard CEO","<p>Yahoo Finance’s Brian Sozzi sits down with Mastercard CEO, Michael Miebach, as they discuss consumer spending, the return of travel, the service industry, and the future of crypto.</p>","Thu, 03 Nov 2022 19:34:00 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Brian Sozzi', 'PERSON'), ('Mastercard', 'ORG'), ('Michael Miebach', 'PERSON')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['p', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'sits', 'Mastercard', 'CEO', 'Michael', 'Miebach', 'discuss', 'consumer', 'spending', 'return', 'travel', 'service', 'industry', 'future']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Home Depot Co-Founder Bernie Marcus,"<p>Yahoo Finance’s Brian Sozzi sits down with Home Depot Co-Founder, Bernie Marcus, as they discuss Bernie's book, ‘Kick Up Some Dust’, the state of the economy, capitalism, and difficulties facing small businesses in the U.S.</p>","Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:51:52 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Brian Sozzi', 'PERSON'), ('Home Depot Co-Founder', 'ORG'), ('Bernie Marcus', 'PERSON'), ('Bernie', 'PERSON')], 'sentiment': -0.20277777777777778, 'keywords': ['p', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'sits', 'Home', 'Depot', 'Co', 'Founder', 'Bernie', 'Marcus', 'discuss', 'Bernie', 'book', 'Kick', 'Dust', 'state', 'economy', 'capitalism', 'difficulties', 'facing', 'small', 'businesses']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Mark Suzman, Bill & Melinda Gates Foundation CEO","<p>Yahoo Finance’s Julie Hyman and Akiko Fujita sit down with Bill &amp; Melinda Gates Foundation CEO, Mark Suzman, to discuss the foundation’s 2022 Goalkeepers Report, world hunger, climate change, and gender equality.</p>","Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:47:46 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Julie Hyman', 'PERSON'), ('Akiko Fujita', 'PERSON'), ('Bill &', 'ORG'), ('Melinda Gates Foundation', 'ORG'), ('Mark Suzman', 'PERSON'), ('2022 Goalkeepers Report', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.15555555555555559, 'keywords': ['p', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Julie', 'Hyman', 'Akiko', 'Fujita', 'sit', 'Bill', 'amp', 'Melinda', 'Gates', 'Foundation', 'CEO', 'Mark', 'Suzman', 'discuss', 'foundation', 'Goalkeepers', 'Report', 'world', 'hunger', 'climate', 'change', 'gender']}","{'numbers': ['2022'], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Chip Brewer, Topgolf Callaway Brands CEO","<p>Yahoo Finance’s Brian Sozzi sits down with Topgolf Callaway Brands CEO, Chip Brewer, at the Goldman Sachs 29th Annual Global Retailing Conference in New York City, as they discuss the company’s name change, Topgolf, hybrid work, and the golf business.</p>","Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:41:35 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Brian Sozzi', 'PERSON'), ('Topgolf Callaway Brands', 'ORG'), ('Chip Brewer', 'PERSON'), ('the Goldman Sachs', 'FAC'), ('29th', 'DATE'), ('New York City', 'GPE'), ('Topgolf', 'PERSON')], 'sentiment': -0.006397306397306411, 'keywords': ['p', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'sits', 'Topgolf', 'Callaway', 'Brands', 'CEO', 'Chip', 'Brewer', 'Goldman', 'Sachs', 'Annual', 'Global', 'Retailing', 'Conference', 'New', 'York', 'City', 'discuss', 'company', 'change', 'Topgolf', 'hybrid', 'work', 'golf']}","{'numbers': ['29th'], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Jay Leno, ‘Jay Leno’s Garage’ Host","<p>Yahoo Finance’s Pras Subramanian sits down with ‘Jay Leno’s Garage’ Host, Jay Leno, at his garage in California, as they discuss Jay’s car collection, Elon Musk, electric vehicles, the seventh season of ‘Jay Leno’s Garage’, and Jay’s line of car care products.</p>","Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:38:37 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Subramanian', 'NORP'), ('Jay Leno’s', 'PERSON'), ('Jay Leno', 'PERSON'), ('California', 'GPE'), ('Jay', 'PERSON'), ('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('the seventh season', 'DATE'), ('Jay Leno’s', 'PERSON'), ('Jay', 'PERSON')], 'sentiment': -0.15555555555555559, 'keywords': ['p', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Pras', 'Subramanian', 'sits', 'Jay', 'Leno', 'Garage', 'Host', 'Jay', 'Leno', 'garage', 'California', 'discuss', 'Jay', 'car', 'collection', 'Elon', 'Musk', 'electric', 'vehicles', 'seventh', 'season', 'Jay', 'Leno', 'Garage', 'Jay', 'line', 'car', 'care']}","{'numbers': ['seventh'], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: World Bank President David Malpass,"<p>World Bank President David Malpass sat down with Yahoo Finance’s Brian Cheung in Jackson Hole, Wyoming to talk about addressing inflation, global inequalities, and the current worry that keeps him up at night.</p>","Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:31:16 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('World Bank', 'ORG'), ('David Malpass', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Brian Cheung', 'PERSON'), ('Jackson Hole', 'GPE'), ('Wyoming', 'GPE')], 'sentiment': -0.051851851851851864, 'keywords': ['p', 'World', 'Bank', 'President', 'David', 'Malpass', 'sat', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Brian', 'Cheung', 'Jackson', 'Hole', 'Wyoming', 'talk', 'addressing', 'inflation', 'global', 'inequalities', 'current', 'worry', 'keeps']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Here's why Kevin Hart teamed up with Fanatics billionaire Michael Rubin to challenge McDonald's,"<p>Actor and comedian Kevin Hart, now restaurant franchise owner, sits down with Brian Sozzi to discuss Hart’s new venture into the fast food business, attracting new investors, and going head-to-head with fast food giants.</p>","Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:30:34 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Kevin Hart', 'PERSON'), ('Brian Sozzi', 'PERSON'), ('Hart', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.10343434343434343, 'keywords': ['p', 'Actor', 'comedian', 'Kevin', 'Hart', 'restaurant', 'franchise', 'owner', 'sits', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'discuss', 'Hart', 'new', 'venture', 'fast', 'food', 'business', 'attracting', 'new', 'investors', 'going', 'head', 'head', 'fast', 'food']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Larry Summers, Fmr U.S. Treasury Secretary","<p>Yahoo Finance’s Jennifer Schonberger is joined by Former NEC Director &amp; Former U.S. Treasury Secretary, Larry Summers, as they discuss the Inflation Reduction Act, inflation in the United States, and the possibility of a recession.</p>","Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:20:00 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Jennifer Schonberger', 'PERSON'), ('NEC', 'ORG'), ('U.S. Treasury', 'ORG'), ('Larry Summers', 'PERSON'), ('the Inflation Reduction Act', 'LAW'), ('the United States', 'GPE')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['p', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Jennifer', 'Schonberger', 'joined', 'NEC', 'Director', 'amp', 'Treasury', 'Secretary', 'Larry', 'Summers', 'discuss', 'Inflation', 'Reduction', 'Act', 'inflation', 'United', 'States', 'possibility']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Moderna CEO Stéphane Bancel,"<p>Moderna CEO Stéphane Bancel sat down with Yahoo Finance’s Anjalee Khemlani to discuss what’s been happening with their covid booster, meeting global vaccine demand, and what other medical areas the company has been focusing on.</p>","Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:16:14 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Moderna', 'PERSON'), ('Stéphane Bancel', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Anjalee Khemlani', 'PERSON')], 'sentiment': -0.07013888888888889, 'keywords': ['p', 'Moderna', 'CEO', 'Stéphane', 'Bancel', 'sat', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Anjalee', 'Khemlani', 'discuss', 'happening', 'covid', 'booster', 'meeting', 'global', 'vaccine', 'demand', 'medical', 'areas', 'company', 'focusing']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Procter & Gamble CEO Jon Moeller,"<p>Procter &amp; Gamble CEO Jon Moeller sits down with Brian Sozzi to discuss micro-economic environment results, what drove the core organic sales, and how consumers are responding to inflation.</p>","Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:08:02 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Procter &amp', 'ORG'), ('Jon Moeller', 'PERSON'), ('Brian Sozzi', 'PERSON')], 'sentiment': -0.15555555555555559, 'keywords': ['p', 'Procter', 'amp', 'Gamble', 'CEO', 'Jon', 'Moeller', 'sits', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'discuss', 'micro', 'economic', 'environment', 'results', 'drove', 'core', 'organic', 'sales', 'consumers', 'responding']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Pete Buttigieg,"<p>U.S. Secretary of Transportation Pete Buttigieg joins Yahoo Finance’s Editor-in-Chief Andy Serwer to discuss the current situation with the airlines, how the money from the infrastructure bill is being distributed and used, as well as his thoughts on the recent vote on same-sex marriage.</p>","Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:03:47 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Transportation', 'ORG'), ('Pete Buttigieg', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Andy Serwer', 'PERSON')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['p', 'Secretary', 'Transportation', 'Pete', 'Buttigieg', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Chief', 'Andy', 'Serwer', 'discuss', 'current', 'situation', 'airlines', 'money', 'infrastructure', 'bill', 'distributed', 'thoughts', 'recent', 'vote', 'sex']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Amos Hochstein,"<p>President Biden's Special Coordinator for International Energy Affairs sits down with Akiko Fujita to discuss where things are going with oil prices, a possible cap on Russian oil prices, and the transition to green energy.</p>","Fri, 21 Oct 2022 14:58:19 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Special Coordinator for International Energy Affairs', 'ORG'), ('Akiko Fujita', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')], 'sentiment': 0.000264550264550259, 'keywords': ['p', 'President', 'Biden', 'Special', 'Coordinator', 'International', 'Energy', 'Affairs', 'sits', 'Akiko', 'Fujita', 'discuss', 'things', 'going', 'oil', 'prices', 'possible', 'cap', 'Russian', 'oil', 'prices', 'transition', 'green']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Fashion Designer Rebecca Minkoff,"Yahoo Finance’s Brian Sozzi speaks with Fashion Designer Rebecca Minkoff at the Goldman Sachs Small Business Symposium about what small business owners should focus on and the possibility of a recession impacting designer bag prices.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 21 Jul 2022 19:49:44 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Brian Sozzi', 'PERSON'), ('Rebecca Minkoff', 'PERSON'), ('the Goldman Sachs Small Business Symposium', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.16666666666666666, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'speaks', 'Fashion', 'Designer', 'Rebecca', 'Minkoff', 'Goldman', 'Sachs', 'Small', 'Business', 'Symposium', 'small', 'business', 'owners', 'focus', 'possibility', 'recession', 'impacting', 'designer', 'bag', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Gina Raimondo,"U.S. Commerce Secretary Gina Raimondo joins Yahoo Finance's Julie Hyman to discuss the semiconductor shortage, the chances Washington will help the problem, and gas prices.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 21 Jul 2022 19:46:42 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Commerce', 'ORG'), ('Gina Raimondo', 'PERSON'), (""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('Julie Hyman', 'PERSON'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Commerce', 'Secretary', 'Gina', 'Raimondo', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Julie', 'Hyman', 'discuss', 'semiconductor', 'shortage', 'chances', 'Washington', 'help', 'problem', 'gas', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Chris Best, Substack Founder & CEO","Yahoo Finance’s Akiko Fujita sits down with Substack Founder &amp; CEO, Chris Best, to discuss the platform’s business model, the media landscape, and three of Chris’ Substack subscriptions.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 20 Jul 2022 19:21:07 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Akiko Fujita', 'PERSON'), ('Substack Founder &', 'ORG'), ('Chris Best', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chris', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.2814814814814815, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Akiko', 'Fujita', 'sits', 'Substack', 'Founder', 'amp', 'CEO', 'Chris', 'Best', 'discuss', 'platform', 'business', 'model', 'media', 'landscape', 'Chris', 'Substack', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': ['three'], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Salesforce Co-CEO & Twitter Chairman Bret Taylor,"Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi sits down with Salesforce Co-CEO &amp; Twitter Chairman Bret Taylor at MuleSoft CONNECT 2022 in New York City to discuss the recent tech sell-off, inflation, remote work, and the direction of Salesforce.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 06 Jul 2022 14:11:13 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Salesforce Co-CEO &amp', 'ORG'), ('Twitter', 'PERSON'), ('Bret Taylor', 'PERSON'), ('MuleSoft', 'PRODUCT'), ('2022', 'DATE'), ('New York City', 'GPE'), ('Salesforce.<br', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.023838383838383846, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'sits', 'Salesforce', 'Co', 'CEO', 'amp', 'Twitter', 'Chairman', 'Bret', 'Taylor', 'MuleSoft', 'CONNECT', 'New', 'York', 'City', 'discuss', 'recent', 'tech', 'sell', 'inflation', 'remote', 'work', 'direction', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': ['2022'], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Baron Davis, Fmr NBA All-Star","Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi sits down with Fmr NBA All-Star, Baron Davis, to discuss investing, the future for NFTs and crypto, and the Golden State Warriors.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 29 Jun 2022 13:49:34 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Fmr NBA All-Star', 'PERSON'), ('Davis', 'PERSON'), ('the Golden State Warriors.<br', 'FAC'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0361111111111111, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'sits', 'Fmr', 'NBA', 'Star', 'Baron', 'Davis', 'discuss', 'investing', 'future', 'NFTs', 'crypto', 'Golden', 'State', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Ryan Reynolds,"Yahoo Finance’s Alexandra Garfinkle sits down with Actor &amp; Mint Mobile Owner, Ryan Reynolds, to discuss his entry into the wireless service industry with Mint Mobile, Ryan’s work in advertising and marketing, and how he spends his money.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 22 Jun 2022 15:41:05 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Alexandra Garfinkle', 'PERSON'), ('Actor &', 'ORG'), ('Mint Mobile Owner', 'ORG'), ('Ryan Reynolds', 'PERSON'), ('Mint Mobile', 'ORG'), ('Ryan', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Alexandra', 'Garfinkle', 'sits', 'Actor', 'amp', 'Mint', 'Mobile', 'Owner', 'Ryan', 'Reynolds', 'discuss', 'entry', 'wireless', 'service', 'industry', 'Mint', 'Mobile', 'Ryan', 'work', 'advertising', 'marketing', 'spends', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Fran Horowitz, Abercrombie & Fitch CEO","Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi sits down with Abercrombie &amp; Fitch CEO, Fran Horowitz, to discuss how the company has changed, clothing trends, new store openings, and Fran’s advice to other leaders.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 22 Jun 2022 13:54:55 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Abercrombie &', 'ORG'), ('Fitch', 'PERSON'), ('Fran Horowitz', 'PERSON'), ('Fran', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.03604797979797981, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'sits', 'Abercrombie', 'amp', 'Fitch', 'CEO', 'Fran', 'Horowitz', 'discuss', 'company', 'changed', 'clothing', 'trends', 'new', 'store', 'openings', 'Fran', 'advice', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Jeffrey Katzenberg & Sujay Jaswa,"Yahoo Finance’s Alexandra Garfinkle sits down with WndrCo Founding Partner &amp; Fmr Walt Disney Studios Chairman, Jeffrey Katzenberg and WndrCo Founding Partner, Sujay Jaswa to discuss Jeffrey’s journey to VC, Sujay’s business philosophy, and WndrCo’s investments.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 16 Jun 2022 15:47:51 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Alexandra Garfinkle', 'PERSON'), ('Founding Partner &', 'ORG'), ('Fmr Walt Disney Studios', 'PERSON'), ('Jeffrey Katzenberg', 'PERSON'), ('Founding Partner', 'PERSON'), ('Sujay Jaswa', 'PERSON'), ('Jeffrey', 'PERSON'), ('VC', 'PERSON'), ('Sujay', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Alexandra', 'Garfinkle', 'sits', 'WndrCo', 'Founding', 'Partner', 'amp', 'Fmr', 'Walt', 'Disney', 'Studios', 'Chairman', 'Jeffrey', 'Katzenberg', 'WndrCo', 'Founding', 'Partner', 'Sujay', 'Jaswa', 'discuss', 'Jeffrey', 'journey', 'VC', 'Sujay', 'business', 'philosophy', 'WndrCo', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: NBA Legend Tracy McGrady and OBL strategic advisor Jeffrey Pollack,"Yahoo Finance anchor Dave Briggs talks with NBA Legend Tracy McGrady and OBL strategic advisor Jeffrey Pollack about the new launch of The Ones Basketball League (OBL). T-Mac also gives his take on the current NBA Finals matchup between the Boston Celtics and Golden State Warriors.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 16 Jun 2022 15:27:06 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Dave Briggs', 'PERSON'), ('NBA Legend Tracy McGrady', 'ORG'), ('Jeffrey Pollack', 'PERSON'), ('The Ones Basketball League', 'ORG'), ('T-Mac', 'ORG'), ('NBA Finals', 'ORG'), ('the Boston Celtics', 'ORG'), ('Golden State Warriors.<br', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.10909090909090909, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'anchor', 'Dave', 'Briggs', 'talks', 'NBA', 'Legend', 'Tracy', 'McGrady', 'OBL', 'strategic', 'advisor', 'Jeffrey', 'Pollack', 'new', 'launch', 'Ones', 'Basketball', 'League', 'OBL', 'T', 'Mac', 'gives', 'current', 'NBA', 'Finals', 'matchup', 'Boston', 'Celtics', 'Golden', 'State', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Marc Randolph, Netflix Co-Founder","Yahoo Finance’s Alexandra Canal sits down with Netflix Co-Founder Marc Randolph to discuss his book ‘That Will Never Work’, Netflix’s longevity, the company’s move towards ads, and their crackdown on password sharing.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 16 Jun 2022 15:18:25 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Alexandra Canal', 'PERSON'), ('Netflix Co-Founder', 'ORG'), ('Marc Randolph', 'PERSON'), ('That Will Never Work’', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Netflix', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Alexandra', 'Canal', 'sits', 'Netflix', 'Co', 'Founder', 'Marc', 'Randolph', 'discuss', 'book', 'Work', 'Netflix', 'longevity', 'company', 'ads', 'crackdown', 'password', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Professor Caitlin Myers,"Myers, a Professor of Economics at Middlebury College, spoke to Yahoo Finance's Rick Newman about her work organizing more than 150 researchers for an amicus brief to the Supreme Court about the economic benefits of women having access to abortion.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 08 Jun 2022 14:42:33 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Myers', 'ORG'), ('Middlebury College', 'ORG'), (""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('Rick Newman', 'PERSON'), ('more than 150', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.175, 'keywords': ['Myers', 'Professor', 'Economics', 'Middlebury', 'College', 'spoke', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Rick', 'Newman', 'work', 'organizing', 'researchers', 'amicus', 'brief', 'Supreme', 'Court', 'economic', 'benefits', 'women', 'having', 'access', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': ['150'], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Patrick Spence, Sonos CEO","Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi sits down with Sonos CEO Patrick Spence to discuss supply shortages, the company’s new products, price points, and the state of tech.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 19 May 2022 14:41:19 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Sonos', 'ORG'), ('Patrick Spence', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.006397306397306411, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'sits', 'Sonos', 'CEO', 'Patrick', 'Spence', 'discuss', 'supply', 'shortages', 'company', 'new', 'products', 'price', 'points', 'state', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Reid Hoffman, Greylock Partner & LinkedIn Co-Founder","Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi sits down with Greylock Partner &amp; LinkedIn Co-Founder Reid Hoffman to talk about the future of the workforce, technology, and Elon Musk's takeover of Twitter.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Mon, 09 May 2022 18:10:50 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Greylock Partner &', 'ORG'), ('LinkedIn Co-Founder', 'ORG'), ('Reid Hoffman', 'PERSON'), (""Elon Musk's"", 'PERSON'), ('Twitter.<br', 'NORP'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.051851851851851864, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'sits', 'Greylock', 'Partner', 'amp', 'LinkedIn', 'Co', 'Founder', 'Reid', 'Hoffman', 'talk', 'future', 'workforce', 'technology', 'Elon', 'Musk', 'takeover', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: (D) Massachusetts Rep. Ayanna Pressley,"(D) Massachusetts Rep. Ayanna Pressley joins Yahoo Finance’s Aarthi Vignesh to discuss President Biden’s openness to canceling student loan debt, how midterms may affect the debt canceling timeline, and the administration ethics on student loans.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Mon, 09 May 2022 18:03:10 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Massachusetts', 'GPE'), ('Ayanna Pressley', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Aarthi Vignesh', 'FAC'), ('Biden', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['D', 'Massachusetts', 'Ayanna', 'Pressley', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Aarthi', 'Vignesh', 'discuss', 'President', 'Biden', 'openness', 'canceling', 'student', 'loan', 'debt', 'midterms', 'affect', 'debt', 'canceling', 'timeline', 'administration', 'ethics', 'student', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Top Senators on Crypto,"Yahoo Finance senior reporter Jennifer Schonberger is joined by Sens. Kirsten Gillibrand (D-NY) and Cynthia Lummis (R-WY) about their upcoming bill to offer a comprehensive plan for crypto regulation.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Mon, 09 May 2022 17:58:04 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Jennifer Schonberger', 'PERSON'), ('Kirsten Gillibrand', 'PERSON'), ('Cynthia Lummis', 'PERSON'), ('WY', 'GPE'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'senior', 'reporter', 'Jennifer', 'Schonberger', 'joined', 'Sens', 'Kirsten', 'Gillibrand', 'D', 'NY', 'Cynthia', 'Lummis', 'R', 'WY', 'upcoming', 'bill', 'offer', 'comprehensive', 'plan', 'crypto', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Ford CEO Jim Farley,"Ford CEO Jim Farley joins Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large and anchor Brian Sozzi to discuss the new era of electric vehicle making at the storied auto giant, the start of F-150 Lightning production in Detroit, the battle against Elon Musk’s Tesla and why this moment is extra special to Farley and his family.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Mon, 09 May 2022 17:54:10 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Ford', 'ORG'), ('Jim Farley', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Brian Sozzi', 'PERSON'), ('F-150 Lightning', 'ORG'), ('Detroit', 'GPE'), ('Elon Musk’s Tesla', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Farley', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0987012987012987, 'keywords': ['Ford', 'CEO', 'Jim', 'Farley', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'anchor', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'discuss', 'new', 'era', 'electric', 'vehicle', 'making', 'storied', 'auto', 'giant', 'start', 'Lightning', 'production', 'Detroit', 'battle', 'Elon', 'Musk', 'Tesla', 'moment', 'extra', 'special', 'Farley', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Tony Fadell, iPhone & iPod co-inventor","Yahoo Finance Tech Editor Dan Howley speaks with iPhone &amp; iPod co-inventor Tony Fadell about his new book 'Build' as well as the future of technology.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 04 May 2022 16:34:28 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance Tech', 'ORG'), ('Dan Howley', 'PERSON'), ('iPhone &', 'ORG'), ('iPod', 'ORG'), ('Tony Fadell', 'PERSON'), (""'Build'"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.04545454545454545, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Tech', 'Editor', 'Dan', 'Howley', 'speaks', 'iPhone', 'amp', 'iPod', 'co', 'inventor', 'Tony', 'Fadell', 'new', 'book', 'Build', 'future', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Richard Cordray, Federal Student Aid COO","Yahoo Finance’s Aarthi Swaminathan sits down with Federal Student Aid Chief Operating Officer Richard Cordray to discuss student loan debt, tuition inflation, and the student loan payment pause.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 27 Apr 2022 16:47:48 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Aarthi Swaminathan', 'ORG'), ('Federal Student Aid Chief Operating', 'ORG'), ('Richard Cordray', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Aarthi', 'Swaminathan', 'sits', 'Federal', 'Student', 'Aid', 'Chief', 'Operating', 'Officer', 'Richard', 'Cordray', 'discuss', 'student', 'loan', 'debt', 'tuition', 'inflation', 'student', 'loan', 'payment', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Rep. Katie Porter,"Rep. Katie Porter (D-CA) spoke to Yahoo Finance's Adriana Belmonte about prescription drug prices, stock trading by members of Congress, and her famous whiteboard.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 27 Apr 2022 16:44:06 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Katie Porter', 'PERSON'), (""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('Adriana Belmonte', 'PERSON'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.25, 'keywords': ['Katie', 'Porter', 'D', 'spoke', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Adriana', 'Belmonte', 'prescription', 'drug', 'prices', 'stock', 'trading', 'members', 'Congress', 'famous', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Rep. Ro Khanna,"Yahoo Finance’s Alexandra Garfinkle sits down with Congressman Ro Khanna of California to discuss the America COMPETES Act, the need for more high-tech production in the United States, the importance of data privacy, and cryptocurrency.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 20 Apr 2022 15:48:57 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Alexandra Garfinkle', 'PERSON'), ('Ro Khanna', 'PERSON'), ('California', 'GPE'), ('the America COMPETES Act', 'EVENT'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.11481481481481481, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Alexandra', 'Garfinkle', 'sits', 'Congressman', 'Ro', 'Khanna', 'California', 'discuss', 'America', 'COMPETES', 'Act', 'need', 'high', 'tech', 'production', 'United', 'States', 'importance', 'data', 'privacy', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Actor Drew Barrymore and Quorn USA President Judd Zusel,"Actor Drew Barrymore and Quorn USA President Judd Zusel join Yahoo Finance’s Brooke DiPalma to discuss their thoughts on Drew Barrymore being named Quorn’s “Chief Mom Officer,” early days in the meat free game, and business food chains embrace meatless.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 20 Apr 2022 15:46:32 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Drew Barrymore', 'PERSON'), ('Quorn USA', 'ORG'), ('Judd Zusel', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Brooke DiPalma', 'PERSON'), ('Drew Barrymore', 'FAC'), ('Quorn', 'PERSON'), ('early days', 'DATE'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.024999999999999994, 'keywords': ['Actor', 'Drew', 'Barrymore', 'Quorn', 'USA', 'President', 'Judd', 'Zusel', 'join', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Brooke', 'DiPalma', 'discuss', 'thoughts', 'Drew', 'Barrymore', 'named', 'Quorn', 'Chief', 'Mom', 'Officer', 'early', 'days', 'meat', 'free', 'game', 'business', 'food', 'chains', 'embrace', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Nick Jordan, Narrative CEO","Yahoo Finance’s Pras Subramanian joins Narrative CEO Nick Jordan at the New York International Auto Show to discuss how auto companies are utilizing data collection.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 20 Apr 2022 15:42:15 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Pras Subramanian', 'ORG'), ('Narrative', 'ORG'), ('Nick Jordan', 'PERSON'), ('the New York International Auto Show', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.04545454545454545, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Pras', 'Subramanian', 'joins', 'Narrative', 'CEO', 'Nick', 'Jordan', 'New', 'York', 'International', 'Auto', 'discuss', 'auto', 'companies', 'utilizing', 'data', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Ark Invest Founder & CEO Cathie Wood,"Yahoo Finance’s Julie Hyman sits down with ARK Invest Founder &amp; CEO Cathie Wood in Miami at the Exchange: An ETF Experience conference to discuss her fund's performance, crypto investing, and her vision for the future of the auto sector.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 20 Apr 2022 15:39:58 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Julie Hyman', 'PERSON'), ('ARK Invest Founder &', 'ORG'), ('Cathie Wood', 'PERSON'), ('Miami', 'GPE'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.051851851851851864, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Julie', 'Hyman', 'sits', 'ARK', 'Invest', 'Founder', 'amp', 'CEO', 'Cathie', 'Wood', 'Miami', 'Exchange', 'ETF', 'Experience', 'conference', 'discuss', 'fund', 'performance', 'crypto', 'investing', 'vision', 'future', 'auto', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: NBA Legend Gary Payton,"NBA legend Gary Payton joins Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large and anchor Brian Sozzi to discuss making the 75 greatest NBA players list, how the game of basketball has changed during the pandemic, and the biggest business lessons he’s learned.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 20 Apr 2022 15:33:05 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('NBA', 'ORG'), ('Gary Payton', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Brian Sozzi', 'PERSON'), ('75', 'CARDINAL'), ('NBA', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.19999999999999998, 'keywords': ['NBA', 'legend', 'Gary', 'Payton', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'anchor', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'discuss', 'making', 'greatest', 'NBA', 'players', 'list', 'game', 'basketball', 'changed', 'pandemic', 'biggest', 'business', 'lessons', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': ['75'], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Levi Strauss CFO Harmit Singh,"Yahoo Finance’s Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi sits down with Levi Strauss CFO Harmit Singh to discuss price increases and inflation, the company’s stores in Russia, and how the CFO role has changed.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 13 Apr 2022 17:16:49 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Levi Strauss', 'PERSON'), ('Singh', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('CFO', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'sits', 'Levi', 'Strauss', 'CFO', 'Harmit', 'Singh', 'discuss', 'price', 'increases', 'inflation', 'company', 'stores', 'Russia', 'CFO', 'role', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Winnie Harlow,"Yahoo Finance’s Alexandra Canal sits down with Supermodel and CAY SKIN Founder Winnie Harlow to discuss her beauty brand CAY SKIN, diversity in the modeling industry, and advice to women in business.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 06 Apr 2022 16:38:40 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Alexandra Canal', 'PERSON'), ('Supermodel', 'ORG'), ('Winnie Harlow', 'PERSON'), ('CAY SKIN', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Alexandra', 'Canal', 'sits', 'Supermodel', 'CAY', 'SKIN', 'Founder', 'Winnie', 'Harlow', 'discuss', 'beauty', 'brand', 'CAY', 'SKIN', 'diversity', 'modeling', 'industry', 'advice', 'women', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Dr. Anthony Fauci,"Director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases Dr. Anthony Fauci joins Yahoo Finance’s Anjalee Khemlani to discuss the pandemic being more manageable, concerns on vaccine efficacy for young and older populations, and COVID funding and fatigue as it stands currently.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 06 Apr 2022 16:36:28 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases', 'ORG'), ('Anthony Fauci', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Anjalee Khemlani', 'PERSON'), ('COVID', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.19166666666666665, 'keywords': ['Director', 'National', 'Institute', 'Allergy', 'Infectious', 'Diseases', 'Anthony', 'Fauci', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Anjalee', 'Khemlani', 'discuss', 'pandemic', 'manageable', 'concerns', 'vaccine', 'efficacy', 'young', 'older', 'populations', 'COVID', 'funding', 'fatigue', 'stands', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: 'What's Your Problem?' Host Jacob Goldstein,"Yahoo Finance’s Brad Smith talks to Jacob Goldstein, host of the new podcast 'What's Your Problem?' and former host of NPR's 'Planet Money' about the rise in podcasts, innovation in fintech, DeFi, and cryptocurrency.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 06 Apr 2022 16:33:23 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Brad Smith', 'PERSON'), ('Jacob Goldstein', 'PERSON'), ('NPR', 'ORG'), (""'Planet Money'"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('DeFi', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.04545454545454545, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Brad', 'Smith', 'talks', 'Jacob', 'Goldstein', 'host', 'new', 'podcast', 'Problem', 'host', 'NPR', 'Planet', 'Money', 'rise', 'podcasts', 'innovation', 'fintech', 'DeFi', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Ray Dalio,"Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi sits down with Bridgewater Associates Founder Ray Dalio to discuss his new animated video <a href=""https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xguam0TKMw8"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">“Principles for Dealing with the Changing World Order”</a> which examines how historical events help us understand what is happening now, and to anticipate what will happen in the future.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 06 Apr 2022 16:20:40 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Bridgewater Associates', 'ORG'), ('Ray Dalio', 'PERSON'), ('the Changing World Order”</a', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.0038383838383838466, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'sits', 'Bridgewater', 'Associates', 'Founder', 'Ray', 'Dalio', 'discuss', 'new', 'animated', 'video', 'noreferrer', 'Dealing', 'Changing', 'World', 'examines', 'historical', 'events', 'help', 'understand', 'happening', 'anticipate', 'happen', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Recording Academy CEO Harvey Mason Jr.,"Recording Academy CEO Harvey Mason Jr. joins Yahoo Finance's Jennifer Schonberger to discuss moving the Grammy’s to Vegas, diversity and inclusion in this year’s show, Foo Fighters special tribute for this year’s show, and NFTs and the future of music.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 06 Apr 2022 16:13:48 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Recording Academy', 'ORG'), ('Harvey Mason Jr.', 'PERSON'), (""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('Jennifer Schonberger', 'PERSON'), ('Grammy', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Vegas', 'GPE'), ('year', 'DATE'), ('Foo Fighters', 'ORG'), ('year', 'DATE'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.11904761904761905, 'keywords': ['Recording', 'Academy', 'CEO', 'Harvey', 'Mason', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Jennifer', 'Schonberger', 'discuss', 'moving', 'Grammy', 'Vegas', 'diversity', 'inclusion', 'year', 'Foo', 'Fighters', 'special', 'tribute', 'year', 'NFTs', 'future', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Sam Kennedy, Red Sox CEO & President and Andrei Cherny, Aspiration CEO","Red Sox CEO &amp; President Sam Kennedy and Aspiration CEO Andrei Cherny join Yahoo Finance anchor and reporter Akiko Fujita to discuss their thoughts on how the Red Sox plan to cut emissions at Fenway Park, sustainability as an investment, and MLB shift to streaming.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 06 Apr 2022 16:08:54 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Red Sox', 'ORG'), ('Sam Kennedy', 'PERSON'), ('Aspiration', 'PRODUCT'), ('Andrei Cherny', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Akiko Fujita', 'PERSON'), ('Red Sox', 'ORG'), ('Fenway Park', 'FAC'), ('MLB', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Red', 'Sox', 'CEO', 'amp', 'President', 'Sam', 'Kennedy', 'Aspiration', 'CEO', 'Andrei', 'Cherny', 'join', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'anchor', 'reporter', 'Akiko', 'Fujita', 'discuss', 'thoughts', 'Red', 'Sox', 'plan', 'cut', 'emissions', 'Fenway', 'Park', 'sustainability', 'investment', 'MLB', 'shift', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Patrick Mahomes,"Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi speaks with NFL All-Pro quarterback Patrick Mahomes about the recent changes to NFL overtime rules, Mahomes business investments with Airshare and Whoop, as well as what to anticipate ahead of the next NFL season.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 31 Mar 2022 17:20:16 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('NFL', 'ORG'), ('Patrick Mahomes', 'PERSON'), ('NFL', 'ORG'), ('Mahomes', 'ORG'), ('Airshare', 'PRODUCT'), ('Whoop', 'ORG'), ('NFL', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'speaks', 'NFL', 'Pro', 'quarterback', 'Patrick', 'Mahomes', 'recent', 'changes', 'NFL', 'overtime', 'rules', 'Mahomes', 'business', 'investments', 'Airshare', 'Whoop', 'anticipate', 'ahead', 'NFL', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Martin Mucci, Paychex CEO","Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi sits down with Paychex CEO Martin Mucci to discuss wage growth, the importance of retaining employees, and inflation.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 30 Mar 2022 16:35:51 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Paychex', 'ORG'), ('Martin Mucci', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'sits', 'Paychex', 'CEO', 'Martin', 'Mucci', 'discuss', 'wage', 'growth', 'importance', 'retaining', 'employees', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: PIMCO founder Bill Gross,"PIMCO founder Bill Gross joins Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large and anchor Brian Sozzi to discuss his thoughts on a possible recession, market and investment cycles, and the stagflation market.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 30 Mar 2022 16:33:09 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Bill Gross', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Brian Sozzi', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['PIMCO', 'founder', 'Bill', 'Gross', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'anchor', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'discuss', 'thoughts', 'possible', 'recession', 'market', 'investment', 'cycles', 'stagflation', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Emma Grede, Good American Co-Founder and CEO","Yahoo Finance’s Dani Romero sits down with Good American Co-Founder and CEO Emma Grede to discuss her company’s ‘Good Inc’ incubator program, her experience as an investor on ‘Shark Tank’, and what it was like to pitch new business ideas to the Kardashians.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 30 Mar 2022 16:26:17 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Dani Romero', 'PERSON'), ('Good American Co-Founder', 'ORG'), ('Emma Grede', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.2301346801346801, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Dani', 'Romero', 'sits', 'Good', 'American', 'Co', 'Founder', 'CEO', 'Emma', 'Grede', 'discuss', 'company', 'Good', 'Inc', 'incubator', 'program', 'experience', 'investor', 'Shark', 'Tank', 'like', 'pitch', 'new', 'business', 'ideas', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Pantera Capital CEO & Founder Dan Morehead,"Pantera Capital CEO &amp; Founder Dan Morehead joins Yahoo Finance reporter Brian Cheung to discuss the outlook on Bitcoin, Blockchain technology, Pantera’s $600 million fund, Bitcoin's future, Blockchain technology, and cryptocurrency opportunities and valuations.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 30 Mar 2022 16:21:44 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Pantera Capital CEO &amp', 'ORG'), ('Dan Morehead', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Brian Cheung', 'PERSON'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('Blockchain', 'PERSON'), ('Pantera', 'ORG'), ('$600 million', 'MONEY'), ('Bitcoin', 'PERSON'), ('Blockchain', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Pantera', 'Capital', 'CEO', 'amp', 'Founder', 'Dan', 'Morehead', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'reporter', 'Brian', 'Cheung', 'discuss', 'outlook', 'Bitcoin', 'Blockchain', 'technology', 'Pantera', 'million', 'fund', 'Bitcoin', 'future', 'Blockchain', 'technology', 'cryptocurrency', 'opportunities', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': ['600', 'million'], 'currencies': ['$600 million']}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Former Jamba Juice CEO James D. White,"Yahoo Finance’s Brad Smith sits down with former Jamba Juice CEO James D. White to discuss his new book ""Anti-Racist Leadership"" and how society can improve diversity and inclusion in the workplace.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 30 Mar 2022 16:13:49 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Brad Smith', 'PERSON'), ('Jamba Juice', 'PERSON'), ('James D. White', 'PERSON'), ('Anti-Racist Leadership', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.0038383838383838466, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Brad', 'Smith', 'sits', 'Jamba', 'Juice', 'CEO', 'James', 'White', 'discuss', 'new', 'book', 'Anti', 'Racist', 'Leadership', 'society', 'improve', 'diversity', 'inclusion', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Aparna Chennapragada, Robinhood Chief Product Officer","Robinhood Chief Product Officer Aparna Chennapragada joins Yahoo Finance's Brad Smith to discuss the launch of a Cash Card for consumer spending trends to unlock its next growth opportunity and improve the accessibility of crypto.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 24 Mar 2022 18:02:49 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Aparna Chennapragada', 'PERSON'), (""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('Brad Smith', 'PERSON'), ('a Cash Card', 'PRODUCT'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Robinhood', 'Chief', 'Product', 'Officer', 'Aparna', 'Chennapragada', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Brad', 'Smith', 'discuss', 'launch', 'Cash', 'Card', 'consumer', 'spending', 'trends', 'unlock', 'growth', 'opportunity', 'improve', 'accessibility', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Nvidia Founder & CEO Jensen Huang,"Yahoo Finance's Daniel Howley and Julie Hyman speak with Nvidia Founder &amp; CEO Jensen Huang about the company's new CPU and GPU tech, as well as what is in store for the future of artificial intelligence and autonomous vehicles.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 24 Mar 2022 16:38:09 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [(""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('Daniel Howley', 'PERSON'), ('Julie Hyman', 'PERSON'), ('Nvidia Founder &', 'ORG'), ('Jensen Huang', 'PERSON'), ('CPU', 'ORG'), ('GPU', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.01272727272727272, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Daniel', 'Howley', 'Julie', 'Hyman', 'speak', 'Nvidia', 'Founder', 'amp', 'CEO', 'Jensen', 'Huang', 'company', 'new', 'CPU', 'GPU', 'tech', 'store', 'future', 'artificial', 'intelligence', 'autonomous', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Affirm Founder Max Levchin,"Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi sits down with Affirm Founder Max Levchin to discuss his childhood, coming to the U.S., the Russia-Ukraine invasion, and Affirm’s company mission.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 23 Mar 2022 13:36:32 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Max Levchin', 'PERSON'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Affirm', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'sits', 'Affirm', 'Founder', 'Max', 'Levchin', 'discuss', 'childhood', 'coming', 'Russia', 'Ukraine', 'invasion', 'Affirm', 'company', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Colorado Gov. Jared Polis,"Polis sits down with Yahoo Finance's Rick Newman to discuss the economy in Colorado, why he wants a suspension of gas taxes, and what a 'digital state' for crypto would look like.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 23 Mar 2022 13:21:09 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [(""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('Rick Newman', 'PERSON'), ('Colorado', 'GPE'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.011111111111111106, 'keywords': ['Polis', 'sits', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Rick', 'Newman', 'discuss', 'economy', 'Colorado', 'wants', 'suspension', 'gas', 'taxes', 'digital', 'state', 'crypto', 'look', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Thomas Peterffy, Chairman and Founder of Interactive Brokers Group","Chairman and Founder of Interactive Brokers Group Thomas Peterffy sits down with Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi to discuss IBKR’s new GlobalTrader app, the state of the stock market, and the Russia-Ukraine war.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 17 Mar 2022 18:06:49 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Founder of Interactive Brokers Group Thomas Peterffy', 'ORG'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('IBKR', 'ORG'), ('GlobalTrader', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.006397306397306411, 'keywords': ['Chairman', 'Founder', 'Interactive', 'Brokers', 'Group', 'Thomas', 'Peterffy', 'sits', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'discuss', 'IBKR', 'new', 'GlobalTrader', 'app', 'state', 'stock', 'market', 'Russia', 'Ukraine', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Reshma Saujani, Girls Who Code Founder","Girls Who Code Founder Reshma Saujani joins Yahoo Finance's Dani Romero to discuss what the future holds for women in the workplace, how working women were affected by COVID-19, and navigating the male-dominated world of crypto.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 17 Mar 2022 18:01:36 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Saujani', 'PERSON'), (""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('Dani Romero', 'PERSON'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Girls', 'Code', 'Founder', 'Reshma', 'Saujani', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Dani', 'Romero', 'discuss', 'future', 'holds', 'women', 'workplace', 'working', 'women', 'affected', 'navigating', 'male', 'dominated', 'world', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: U.S. Secretary of Transportation Pete Buttigieg,"Yahoo Finance’s Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi talks with U.S. Secretary of Transportation Pete Buttigieg about the new Freight Logistics Optimization Works (FLOW) initiative aimed at data sharing as well as the topics of supply chain issues and inflation.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 17 Mar 2022 17:56:11 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Transportation', 'ORG'), ('Pete Buttigieg', 'PERSON'), ('Freight Logistics Optimization Works', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.06818181818181818, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'talks', 'Secretary', 'Transportation', 'Pete', 'Buttigieg', 'new', 'Freight', 'Logistics', 'Optimization', 'Works', 'FLOW', 'initiative', 'aimed', 'data', 'sharing', 'topics', 'supply', 'chain', 'issues', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: SXSW: Austin Mayor Steve Adler,"Austin Mayor Steve Adler sits down with Yahoo Finance Anchor Julie Hyman at SXSW to discuss companies moving to Austin, Tesla’s presence in the city, and rising housing costs.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 17 Mar 2022 17:40:50 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Austin', 'PERSON'), ('Steve Adler', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('SXSW', 'ORG'), ('Austin', 'GPE'), ('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['Austin', 'Mayor', 'Steve', 'Adler', 'sits', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Anchor', 'Julie', 'Hyman', 'SXSW', 'discuss', 'companies', 'moving', 'Austin', 'Tesla', 'presence', 'city', 'rising', 'housing', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Drew Timme, Gonzaga Men’s Basketball Player","Gonzaga Men’s Basketball Player Drew Timme sits down with Yahoo Finance’s Dave Briggs to discuss partnering with Dollar Shave Club, how players are earning money in college basketball, and Gonzaga working toward the national title.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 17 Mar 2022 17:37:10 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Gonzaga Men’s Basketball Player', 'ORG'), ('Drew Timme', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Dave Briggs', 'PERSON'), ('Dollar Shave Club', 'ORG'), ('Gonzaga', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['Gonzaga', 'Men', 'Basketball', 'Player', 'Drew', 'Timme', 'sits', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Dave', 'Briggs', 'discuss', 'partnering', 'Dollar', 'Shave', 'Club', 'players', 'earning', 'money', 'college', 'basketball', 'Gonzaga', 'working', 'national', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Vero Villasenor, Hershey VP of U.S. Confection","Hershey VP of U.S. Confection Vero Villasenor sits down with Yahoo Finance reporter Brooke DiPalma to discuss her career journey at The Hershey Company, the company’s “Celebrate SHE” campaign, and share career advice.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 17 Mar 2022 17:32:55 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Hershey VP', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Vero Villasenor', 'GPE'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Brooke DiPalma', 'PERSON'), ('The Hershey Company', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['Hershey', 'VP', 'Confection', 'Vero', 'Villasenor', 'sits', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'reporter', 'Brooke', 'DiPalma', 'discuss', 'career', 'journey', 'Hershey', 'Company', 'company', 'Celebrate', 'campaign', 'share', 'career', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Petco CEO Ron Coughlin,"Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi sits down at the Nasdaq with Petco CEO Ron Coughlin to break down the company's quarterly growth, inflation, and the massive rise in pet ownership during the COVID-19 pandemic.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 09 Mar 2022 22:14:07 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Petco', 'ORG'), ('Ron Coughlin', 'PERSON'), ('quarterly', 'DATE'), ('COVID-19', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.07777777777777779, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'sits', 'Nasdaq', 'Petco', 'CEO', 'Ron', 'Coughlin', 'break', 'company', 'quarterly', 'growth', 'inflation', 'massive', 'rise', 'pet', 'ownership', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Fidelity Investments CFO Maggie Serravalli,"Fidelity Investments CFO Maggie Serravalli joins Yahoo Finance to share her success story as we celebrate International Women's Day.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 09 Mar 2022 22:08:38 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Fidelity Investments', 'ORG'), ('Maggie Serravalli', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), (""International Women's"", 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.09999999999999999, 'keywords': ['Fidelity', 'Investments', 'CFO', 'Maggie', 'Serravalli', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'share', 'success', 'story', 'celebrate', 'International', 'Women', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Suzi Weiss-Fischmann, OPI Co-Founder","Yahoo Finance senior correspondent Alexandra Canal speaks with Suzi Weiss-Fischmann, OPI Co-Founder about International Women's Day, how she built OPI, and the company's collaboration with Xbox.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 09 Mar 2022 22:04:10 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Alexandra Canal', 'PERSON'), ('Suzi Weiss-Fischmann', 'ORG'), ('OPI Co-Founder', 'ORG'), ('OPI', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'senior', 'correspondent', 'Alexandra', 'Canal', 'speaks', 'Suzi', 'Weiss', 'Fischmann', 'OPI', 'Co', 'Founder', 'International', 'Women', 'Day', 'built', 'OPI', 'company', 'collaboration', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Meta VP Global Business Nicola Mendelsohn,"Yahoo Finance's Julie Hyman speaks with Meta VP of Global Business Nicola Mendelsohn about Meta's work in helping women-led small businesses as well as Mark Zuckerberg's vision for the company.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 09 Mar 2022 21:56:36 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [(""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('Julie Hyman', 'PERSON'), ('Meta VP of', 'ORG'), ('Global Business Nicola Mendelsohn', 'ORG'), ('Meta', 'ORG'), (""Mark Zuckerberg's"", 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.08333333333333333, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Julie', 'Hyman', 'speaks', 'Meta', 'VP', 'Global', 'Business', 'Nicola', 'Mendelsohn', 'Meta', 'work', 'helping', 'women', 'led', 'small', 'businesses', 'Mark', 'Zuckerberg', 'vision', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Nasdaq CEO Adena Friedman,"Yahoo Finance's Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi speaks with Nasdaq CEO Adena Friedman about her journey at the company as well as how she balances her career and motherhood.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 09 Mar 2022 21:41:32 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [(""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('Nasdaq', 'ORG'), ('Adena Friedman', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'speaks', 'Nasdaq', 'CEO', 'Adena', 'Friedman', 'journey', 'company', 'balances', 'career', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Airbnb CEO Brian Chesky,"Yahoo Finance reporter Akiko Fujita speaks with Airbnb CEO Brian Chesky about free housing for up to 100,000 Ukrainian refugees and Airbnb’s mission.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 02 Mar 2022 21:35:24 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Akiko Fujita', 'PERSON'), ('Airbnb', 'ORG'), ('Brian Chesky', 'PERSON'), ('up to 100,000 Ukrainian', 'PERCENT'), ('Airbnb', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.2, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'reporter', 'Akiko', 'Fujita', 'speaks', 'Airbnb', 'CEO', 'Brian', 'Chesky', 'free', 'housing', 'Ukrainian', 'refugees', 'Airbnb', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': ['100,000'], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Crypto Entrepreneur Cordell Broadus,"Crypto Entrepreneur Cordell Broadus joins Yahoo Finance's Jennifer Schonberger to discuss getting involved in NFTs and crypto with his father Snoop Dogg, crypto’s next generation, and NFTs inspired by Snoop Dogg’s career moments.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 02 Mar 2022 21:30:42 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Crypto Entrepreneur', 'PERSON'), ('Cordell Broadus', 'PERSON'), (""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('Jennifer Schonberger', 'PERSON'), ('Snoop Dogg', 'PRODUCT'), ('Snoop Dogg’s', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Crypto', 'Entrepreneur', 'Cordell', 'Broadus', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Jennifer', 'Schonberger', 'discuss', 'getting', 'involved', 'NFTs', 'crypto', 'father', 'Snoop', 'Dogg', 'crypto', 'generation', 'NFTs', 'inspired', 'Snoop', 'Dogg', 'career', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Dr. Patrick Soon-Shiong,"ImmunityBio Executive Chairman Dr. Patrick Soon-Shiong joins Yahoo Finance's Anjalee Khemlani to discuss President Joe Biden’s Cancer Moonshot Initiative, cancer research progress, and his plans to bring South African medical innovation 'to the forefront of the world.’<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 24 Feb 2022 18:29:32 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('ImmunityBio Executive', 'ORG'), ('Patrick Soon-Shiong', 'PERSON'), (""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('Anjalee Khemlani', 'PERSON'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Cancer Moonshot Initiative', 'PERSON'), ('South African', 'NORP'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['ImmunityBio', 'Executive', 'Chairman', 'Patrick', 'Soon', 'Shiong', 'joins', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Anjalee', 'Khemlani', 'discuss', 'President', 'Joe', 'Biden', 'Cancer', 'Moonshot', 'Initiative', 'cancer', 'research', 'progress', 'plans', 'bring', 'South', 'African', 'medical', 'innovation', 'forefront', 'world', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Former CFTC Chairman J. Christopher Giancarlo,"Yahoo Finance senior reporter David Hollerith speaks with former Commodity Futures Trading Commission Chairman J. Christopher Giancarlo about spot market regulation and the CFTC’s role in cryptocurrency.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 24 Feb 2022 18:22:34 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('David Hollerith', 'PERSON'), ('Commodity Futures Trading Commission', 'ORG'), ('J. Christopher Giancarlo', 'PERSON'), ('CFTC', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'senior', 'reporter', 'David', 'Hollerith', 'speaks', 'Commodity', 'Futures', 'Trading', 'Commission', 'Chairman', 'Christopher', 'Giancarlo', 'spot', 'market', 'regulation', 'CFTC', 'role', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
"Yahoo Finance Presents: Music mogul, entrepreneur, & philanthropist Master P","Yahoo Finance's Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi speaks with music mogul Master P on why he is getting into the snack business, his latest business ventures, and what he learned from the COVID-19 pandemic.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 24 Feb 2022 18:10:08 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [(""Yahoo Finance's"", 'ORG'), ('COVID-19', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.25, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'speaks', 'music', 'mogul', 'Master', 'P', 'getting', 'snack', 'business', 'latest', 'business', 'ventures', 'learned', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: NYSE President Lynn Martin,"Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi speaks with the new NYSE President Lynn Martin about her priorities for her new role as well as the future of the trading floor and the 2022 IPO market.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 24 Feb 2022 17:53:57 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('NYSE', 'ORG'), ('Lynn Martin', 'PERSON'), ('2022', 'DATE'), ('IPO', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.06818181818181818, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'speaks', 'new', 'NYSE', 'President', 'Lynn', 'Martin', 'priorities', 'new', 'role', 'future', 'trading', 'floor', 'IPO', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': ['2022'], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce,"Yahoo Finance senior reporter Jennifer Schonberger is joined by SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce to discuss regulation around cryptocurrency exchanges, digital assets, as well as NFTs and Stablecoins. <br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 03 Feb 2022 18:29:35 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Jennifer Schonberger', 'PERSON'), ('SEC', 'ORG'), ('Hester Peirce', 'PERSON'), ('Stablecoins', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.03333333333333333, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'senior', 'reporter', 'Jennifer', 'Schonberger', 'joined', 'SEC', 'Commissioner', 'Hester', 'Peirce', 'discuss', 'regulation', 'cryptocurrency', 'exchanges', 'digital', 'assets', 'NFTs', 'Stablecoins', 'br', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Ford CEO Jim Farley,"On this episode of Yahoo Finance Presents, Yahoo Finance Editor-at-Large Brian Sozzi talks with Ford President &amp; CEO Jim Farley to discuss the company’s Ford Pro program. Also discussed was the recent supply and chip shortage in the auto industry and the expansion of Ford’s electric vehicles vs. their competitors.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Wed, 26 Jan 2022 18:31:36 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance Presents', 'ORG'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Ford President &', 'ORG'), ('Jim Farley', 'PERSON'), ('Ford', 'ORG'), ('Ford', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['episode', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Presents', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Editor', 'Large', 'Brian', 'Sozzi', 'talks', 'Ford', 'President', 'amp', 'CEO', 'Jim', 'Farley', 'discuss', 'company', 'Ford', 'Pro', 'program', 'discussed', 'recent', 'supply', 'chip', 'shortage', 'auto', 'industry', 'expansion', 'Ford', 'electric', 'vehicles', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Brian Deese,"White House Director of the National Economic Council Brian Deese sat down with Yahoo Finance’s Akiko Fujita and Adam Shapiro to discuss how Biden is faring one year into his presidency, and the strides the administration is taking to tackle infrastructure, climate change, and the coronavirus pandemic.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Mon, 24 Jan 2022 19:19:09 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('White House', 'ORG'), ('the National Economic Council Brian Deese', 'ORG'), ('Yahoo Finance’s', 'ORG'), ('Akiko Fujita', 'PERSON'), ('Adam Shapiro', 'PERSON'), ('Biden', 'PERSON'), ('one year', 'DATE'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.011111111111111106, 'keywords': ['White', 'House', 'Director', 'National', 'Economic', 'Council', 'Brian', 'Deese', 'sat', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Akiko', 'Fujita', 'Adam', 'Shapiro', 'discuss', 'Biden', 'faring', 'year', 'presidency', 'strides', 'administration', 'taking', 'tackle', 'infrastructure', 'climate', 'change', 'coronavirus', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': ['one'], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Senator Mark Kelly,"On this episode of Yahoo Finance Presents, Senator Mark Kelly of Arizona talks with Yahoo Finance anchor and reporter Akiko Fujita to discuss the impact inflation is having on the U.S. economy as well as the proposed legislation to limit members of Congress trading stocks. Senator Kelly also discusses more proposed legislation around building and sourcing the U.S. supply of rare earth metals outside of China.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Fri, 21 Jan 2022 14:39:22 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance Presents', 'ORG'), ('Mark Kelly', 'PERSON'), ('Arizona', 'GPE'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('Akiko Fujita', 'PERSON'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Kelly', 'PERSON'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.2, 'keywords': ['episode', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Presents', 'Senator', 'Mark', 'Kelly', 'Arizona', 'talks', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'anchor', 'reporter', 'Akiko', 'Fujita', 'discuss', 'impact', 'inflation', 'having', 'economy', 'proposed', 'legislation', 'limit', 'members', 'Congress', 'trading', 'stocks', 'Senator', 'Kelly', 'discusses', 'proposed', 'legislation', 'building', 'sourcing', 'supply', 'rare', 'earth', 'metals', 'outside', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Influencers with Andy Serwer: Michael Eric Dyson,"In this episode of Influencers, Andy is joined by 'Long Time Coming' author, Michael Eric Dyson for a discussion about race in America and what we as a society can do to address issues of inequality.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 10 Dec 2020 19:40:08 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Influencers', 'NORP'), ('Andy', 'PERSON'), ('Michael Eric Dyson', 'PERSON'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.025, 'keywords': ['episode', 'Influencers', 'Andy', 'joined', 'Long', 'Time', 'Coming', 'author', 'Michael', 'Eric', 'Dyson', 'discussion', 'race', 'America', 'society', 'address', 'issues', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Melinda Gates,"Yahoo Finance Presents: Melinda Gates<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 10 Dec 2020 19:30:31 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance Presents', 'ORG'), ('Melinda', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Presents', 'Melinda', 'Gates', 'br', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Slava Rubin,"Yahoo Finance Presents: Slava Rubin<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 10 Dec 2020 19:22:47 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance Presents', 'ORG'), ('Slava Rubin<br', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Presents', 'Slava', 'Rubin', 'br', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Paul Tudor Jones,"Yahoo Finance Presents: Paul Tudor Jones<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 10 Dec 2020 18:52:23 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance Presents', 'ORG'), ('Paul Tudor Jones', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Presents', 'Paul', 'Tudor', 'Jones', 'br', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: HP CEO Enrique Lores,"Yahoo Finance Presents: HP CEO Enrique Lores<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 10 Dec 2020 18:39:05 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance Presents', 'ORG'), ('Enrique Lores', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Presents', 'HP', 'CEO', 'Enrique', 'Lores', 'br', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Pattern Founder & CEO Tracee Ellis Ross,"Yahoo Finance Presents: Pattern Founder &amp; CEO Tracee Ellis Ross<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Tue, 08 Dec 2020 14:20:30 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance Presents', 'ORG'), ('Pattern Founder &', 'ORG'), ('Tracee Ellis', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Presents', 'Pattern', 'Founder', 'amp', 'CEO', 'Tracee', 'Ellis', 'Ross', 'br', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Influencers with Andy Serwer: Aaron Levie,"In this episode of Influencers, Box Co-Founder and CEO Aaron Levie joins Andy to discuss the cloud computing business, big tech regulation, and how President Trump's immigration policies are hurting American innovation.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Tue, 08 Dec 2020 14:15:02 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Influencers', 'NORP'), ('Aaron Levie', 'PERSON'), ('Andy', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['episode', 'Influencers', 'Box', 'Co', 'Founder', 'CEO', 'Aaron', 'Levie', 'joins', 'Andy', 'discuss', 'cloud', 'computing', 'business', 'big', 'tech', 'regulation', 'President', 'Trump', 'immigration', 'policies', 'hurting', 'American', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: New York Senator Kirsten Gillibrand,"Yahoo Finance Presents: New York Senator Kirsten Gillibrand<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Tue, 08 Dec 2020 14:10:14 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance Presents', 'ORG'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Kirsten Gillibrand', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.06818181818181818, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Presents', 'New', 'York', 'Senator', 'Kirsten', 'Gillibrand', 'br', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Richmond Fed President Tom Barkin,"Yahoo Finance Presents: Richmond Fed President Tom Barkin<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Tue, 08 Dec 2020 14:05:28 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance Presents', 'ORG'), ('Richmond Fed', 'ORG'), ('Tom Barkin', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Presents', 'Richmond', 'Fed', 'President', 'Tom', 'Barkin', 'br', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Yahoo Finance Presents: Darius Miles & Quentin Richardson,"Yahoo Finance Presents: Darius Miles &amp; Quentin Richardson<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Tue, 08 Dec 2020 14:02:27 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Yahoo Finance Presents', 'ORG'), ('Darius Miles &', 'ORG'), ('Quentin Richardson', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Yahoo', 'Finance', 'Presents', 'Darius', 'Miles', 'amp', 'Quentin', 'Richardson', 'br', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Influencers with Andy Serwer: Emmanuel Acho,"In this episode of Influencers, Andy speaks with former NFL player and 'Uncomfortable Conversations with a Black Man' author, Emmanuel Acho, about opening a dialogue about race and address the issue of racism in America.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Tue, 08 Dec 2020 13:59:06 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Influencers', 'NORP'), ('Andy', 'PERSON'), ('NFL', 'ORG'), ('Uncomfortable', 'PRODUCT'), ('Emmanuel Acho', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': -0.16666666666666666, 'keywords': ['episode', 'Influencers', 'Andy', 'speaks', 'NFL', 'player', 'Uncomfortable', 'Conversations', 'Black', 'Man', 'author', 'Emmanuel', 'Acho', 'opening', 'dialogue', 'race', 'address', 'issue', 'racism', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Influencers with Andy Serwer: Matthew McConaughey,"In this episode of Influencers, Andy is joined by Academy Award winning actor and 'Greenlights' author, Matthew McConaughey, as they discuss mental health, money, and the keys to living a happy and successful life.<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Tue, 08 Dec 2020 13:50:24 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Influencers', 'NORP'), ('Andy', 'PERSON'), ('Academy Award', 'ORG'), ('Greenlights', 'PERSON'), ('Matthew McConaughey', 'PERSON'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.39, 'keywords': ['episode', 'Influencers', 'Andy', 'joined', 'Academy', 'Award', 'winning', 'actor', 'Greenlights', 'author', 'Matthew', 'McConaughey', 'discuss', 'mental', 'health', 'money', 'keys', 'living', 'happy', 'successful', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Influencers with Andy Serwer: Reid Hoffman,"<p>In this episode of Influencers, Andy speaks with LinkedIn Co-Founder and Greylock Partner, Reid Hoffman, about the incoming Biden administration, big tech regulation, fighting misinformation on social media, and what's in store for U.S. / China relations.</p><p><br /></p><br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Thu, 12 Nov 2020 14:52:03 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Influencers', 'NORP'), ('Andy', 'PERSON'), ('LinkedIn Co-Founder', 'ORG'), ('Greylock Partner', 'ORG'), ('Reid Hoffman', 'PERSON'), ('Biden', 'PERSON'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.011111111111111112, 'keywords': ['p', 'episode', 'Influencers', 'Andy', 'speaks', 'LinkedIn', 'Co', 'Founder', 'Greylock', 'Partner', 'Reid', 'Hoffman', 'incoming', 'Biden', 'administration', 'big', 'tech', 'regulation', 'fighting', 'misinformation', 'social', 'media', 'store', 'China', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Shantanu Narayen | All Markets Summit by Yahoo Finance,"Shantanu Narayen | All Markets Summit by Yahoo Finance<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Tue, 10 Nov 2020 20:39:12 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Shantanu Narayen', 'ORG'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Shantanu', 'Narayen', 'Markets', 'Summit', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'br', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Paul Scialla | All Markets Summit by Yahoo Finance,"Paul Scialla | All Markets Summit by Yahoo Finance<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Tue, 10 Nov 2020 20:32:25 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Paul Scialla', 'PERSON'), ('All Markets Summit', 'ORG'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Paul', 'Scialla', 'Markets', 'Summit', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'br', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
LL Cool J | All Markets Summit by Yahoo Finance,"LL Cool J | All Markets Summit by Yahoo Finance<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Tue, 10 Nov 2020 20:28:21 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('LL Cool J', 'ORG'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.175, 'keywords': ['LL', 'Cool', 'J', 'Markets', 'Summit', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'br', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
Glenn Fogel | All Markets Summit by Yahoo Finance,"Glenn Fogel | All Markets Summit by Yahoo Finance<br /><p> See <a href=""https://acast.com/privacy"" rel=""noopener noreferrer"" target=""_blank"">acast.com/privacy</a> for privacy and opt-out information.</p>","Tue, 10 Nov 2020 20:22:22 -0000",,https://rss.art19.com/yahoofinancepresents,2024-11-09T17:44:04.297164,"{'entities': [('Glenn Fogel', 'PERSON'), ('Yahoo Finance', 'ORG'), ('href=""https://acast.com', 'ORG')], 'sentiment': 0.0, 'keywords': ['Glenn', 'Fogel', 'Markets', 'Summit', 'Yahoo', 'Finance', 'br', 'privacy', 'noreferrer', 'privacy', 'opt']}","{'numbers': [], 'currencies': []}"
